<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<dolls>
<doll>
<title>Porcelain Dolls</title>
<headline>Posted by</headline>
<author>TheDoll</author>
<text>Dolls have been made from white porcelain since the 18th century. The glazed versions of these antique dolls are generally referred to as china dolls, while the unglazed ones are called bisque dolls.
			In recent years, the interest in antique china dolls has spurred a resurgence in porcelain doll production, which, since the 1970s, has emphasized fine detailing and high levels of craftsmanship.
			These standards apply to porcelain dolls in modern dress as well as those styled after traditional characters wearing vintage attire.</text>
</doll>
<doll>
<title>Plastic Dolls</title>
<headline>Posted by</headline>
<author>TheDoll</author>
<text>Hard-plastic dolls were first introduced in the late '40s, when new plastics developed during World War II were adopted by civilian manufacturers. 
			Well-established doll makers like Alexander Doll Company and Ideal Toy Company started producing many of their most popular doll lines in hard plastic
			instead of the more expensive, more labor-intensive, and less durable materials of dolls past—composition, bisque, or china. 
			They were also quick to forego earlier plastics like rubber and celluloid, which wore out easily. 
			In the case of celluloid, the dolls were also highly flammable.</text>
</doll>

<doll>
<title>Wooden Dolls</title>
<headline>Posted by</headline>
<author>TheDoll</author>
<text>Most early wooden dolls were made in England from 1680 until the early 1800s. 
			They are often called Queen Anne dolls, although most were made before and after her reign. 
			Although far more female wooden dolls were produced, some male dolls were made, the only difference between the two being their dress and hair.

Many wooden dolls were originally created by parents in traditional folk art style, but the most elaborate examples were made by professional craftsmen..</text>
</doll>
<doll>
<title>Ragdolls</title>
<headline>Posted by</headline>
<author>TheDoll</author>
<text>Probably since humans have been making clothes out of fabric, they’ve made dolls for their kids. 
			In fact, the British Museum possesses a rare, well-preserved linen doll from the early Roman Empire. 
			Often these homemade cloth or “rag dolls”—the term for dolls constructed out of any kind of fabric—are pieced 
			together from rags and scraps of fabric found around the house, although they also can be created from high-quality cotton, silk, 
			velvet, or felt.</text>
</doll>
</dolls>